In the criminal justice system.
the people are represented
by two separate. yet
equally important groups:
the police. who
investigate crime.
and the district attorneys.
who prosecute the offenders.
These are their stories.
It's a great opportunity. but
these kids are like family.
I believe in loyalty.
I wish I didn't. I swear to God.
Life would be easier.
But this is my life.
You don't get many
opportunities like this.
- [whistles]
- Hey. I gotta go.
Yeah.
Thanks for listening.
[low suspenseful music]
♪
Two shots to the chest.
Guy over there said he heard
gunshots and called 911.
Didn't see the shooter. though.
Wallet and phone weren't
found on his person.
But it's Nick Walsh.
The coach?
That's him.
Big fan.
Not easy to go back-to-back
in college basketball.
Kentucky just offered this guy
100 mil for five years.
One more data point
that life ain't fair.
Perp snatched his watch.
Snatched a lot more than that.
[tense music]
[dramatic music]
♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
All right. Thanks
for your help.
So the question is.
what was a big-time
college coach doing
down here anyway?
Can someone tell me how in 2024
there's not a single camera
on one of these buildings?
[phone ringing]
Riley.
Yeah. I'll be there in five.
Hey. man. I got
a personal thing.
I'll be back.
I really appreciate
the call. Ray.
Of course. I wish
I knew beforehand.
Yeah. me too. but here we are.
[sighs] Unbelievable.
[chuckles] Vinny.
how you doing. man?
Hey. they set me up.
- Mm.
What do you call
that. entrapment?
- Oh. you're a lawyer now. huh?
- Come on. man.
I didn't have a
choice. all right?
I need the money.
- Oh. you didn't have a choice.
You didn't have a
choice but to sell guns.
Is that what you're
saying to me?
All right. I hear you.
All right. I messed up.
You're right.
Thanks for coming
down. I appreciate it.
Good to see you too.
My partner and I
have been working
that neighborhood
for a few weeks.
putting out word we
were looking for guns.
- Yeah. and then what?
- Matt texted me.
Said he had two heaters
he was trying to move.
So we met up earlier today.
I gave him two grand.
He gave me two guns.
And we busted him.
The guy can't get
out of his own way.
[sighs]
But he's my brother.
and I love him. so...
I get it. Vince.
but we're talking
about guns here.
Hard to make a case
like this disappear.
I understand.
Listen. Matt runs with
a colorful crowd...
hustlers. some real criminals.
Maybe he can work it
off as an informant.
Let me run it up the flagpole.
I owe you one. Ray.
Selling guns. That is no joke.
What was he thinking?
- Man. I... [sighs]
I don't even know
where to begin.
You don't have to.
It's not your job.
You're not your
brother's keeper.
Yeah. sometimes I'm
not so sure about that.
But he's a good guy...
sometimes.
- A good guy who sells guns.
95% of the time he's
all right. you know?
Like when our dad got
sick. he stepped up.
He took care of him.
no questions asked.
Wasn't looking for a
medal. He just did it.
It's the other 5% with Matt.
And he just has a way
of finding trouble. man.
He just digs himself
into hole after hole.
and I am always the one
that has to dig him out.
Mrs. Walsh. I know
how difficult this is.
and I am very sorry
for your loss.
You mentioned that you had
just spoken to your husband.
Do you know what time that was?
Around 4:00.
Do you know where he was?
Who he might have been with?
No.
We were talking about
whether to stay or go.
Kentucky made a
really generous offer.
more than double what
we're making now. but...
but Nick really loved Hudson
and his coaches and his players.
He's just so damn principled.
It was making
everything really hard.
Ma'am. did your husband wear
a watch on his left wrist?
Can you describe it?
It's a Rolex with a platinum
and gold band and a blue face.
Any inscriptions on it?
No.
Why?
The watch was
missing. so we're just
collecting information
at this point.
Was anyone harassing or
threatening your husband?
Not that I'm aware
of. [sniffles]
But the past few
weeks have been crazy.
It felt like the whole city was
threatening and harassing us.
People would walk up
to us in a restaurant.
You can't leave us. Coach.
My whole world revolves
around Hudson basketball.
Actually. I saw him
arguing with someone
outside of our building.
[suspenseful music]
- When was this?
- Two days ago.
So the wife was home
most of the day.
By all appearances. they
had a great relationship.
They met in college.
got married at 24.
- American dream.
- Something like that.
Yo!
Hey. I found a video of
Walsh arguing with somebody.
Check this out.
Can you zoom in
on the other guy?
That's the best I can do.
Wait. Freeze it there.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's a badge.
And it's not NYPD.
Walsh was arguing
with an FBI agent.
♪
I met with Walsh three days ago.
Looked more like
an argument to me.
Yeah. he ran hot.
Lots of emotion.
Was this conversation
personal or professional?
Professional.
Some rich alumnus threatened
to destroy his life.
Why?
Because he was thinking
about leaving Hudson?
Crazy. right?
But these boosters take
this stuff very seriously.
And according to Walsh.
this guy had the resources
and the conviction
to pull it off.
He got nervous.
Called an agent down in
Atlanta... his cousin. I think.
She asked if I could help out.
Why was Walsh so mad?
He changed his mind.
He said he didn't wanna get
this booster in trouble.
Said he overreacted.
When I made it clear that
it wasn't that easy...
genie's out of the bottle...
he got upset.
- Hmm.
This booster got a name?
I just wrote that
stubborn Irish prick
a check for $2 million.
and he's thinking of
walking out on me.
heading to Kentucky?
- Wait. hold on.
You wrote a check
for 2 mil for what?
A 6'7" point guard from LA
who plays defense
like Gary Payton
and shoots like Ray Allen.
Number one recruit
in the country.
Kid's agent wanted 3 mil.
I was able to get it done
for 2 with a 500.000 kicker
if we win the championship.
All this money to play
college basketball now.
Yeah. no rules anymore.
It's the Wild West.
It's really fun.
- Oh. it's fun.
Like getting shot in the chest
in a vacant lot kind of fun?
Yeah. that's...
I can't believe
he's really gone.
I've been crying like a
baby ever since I found out.
You've been crying like a
baby since he's been gone.
and you've been threatening
to ruin his life?
Correct.
The threat had to
do with business.
I pledged 10 million
for a new practice
facility this year.
That's on top of the 2
million for the kid from LA
So I'm long 12 mil
just this year.
And he's gonna walk out on me?
Hell. no. But as a
person. I loved him.
I mean. where I'm from.
you don't try to destroy
the people you love. but...
- I threatened to destroy him.
I was just negotiating.
Look. I wanted to scare
him. to keep him in Hudson.
Where were you the day of
the murder at 4:30 p.m.?
In a meeting here
with 20 people.
Look. I didn't kill Coach Walsh.
Any idea what he was doing
on the Lower East Side?
No.
Any of his friends live there?
Not that I know of.
One of his players does. though.
Well. former player. actually.
Coach cut him from the
team three days ago.
The kid get upset about that?
I'm not sure. His
father was. though.
He went crazy.
I can't say I blame him. either.
Cost the kid a million bucks.
You think the father
is capable of violence?
For a million dollars?
Anyone is.
[tense music]
♪
We hung out for about an hour.
Was that typical?
Was there any reason
Coach was there?
I guess he felt bad and
wanted to make it right.
If you ask me.
that son of a bitch
needed to make it right.
- Yeah. I get it.
Cost Malik a lot of
money. You too. huh?
$1 million.
And he just... he didn't care.
Told Malik to go home.
He had no right to do that.
You feel the same
way about that?
I mean. I was...
I was upset. but...
- What?
- It was my fault.
I wasn't as focused
as I should have been.
I was late to practice a lot.
I was focusing on things
other than basketball.
you know. getting endorsements.
doing TikToks. rapping.
So I get it.
What time did Coach
leave the house?
Around 4:00.
And that's the last
time you guys saw him.
Yes. sir.
Did Walsh say anything
about where he was going
or if he was meeting anybody?
Coach came in
around 4:15 or so.
He was here for
about 20 minutes.
You happen to see who
he was talking to?
I'm pretty sure he was alone...
most of the time. anyway.
But I gotta be honest.
I wasn't really
paying attention.
Was he alone when he left?
Uh. sorry. I didn't notice.
How about was anybody
bothering or harassing him?
Nah.
People here mind
their own business.
Do you mind if we take a look
at your surveillance video?
Don't have any.
Nothing?
Like I said. people here tend
to mind their own business.
All right. Thank you.
Learn anything new?
Yeah. that. apparently.
college basketball is
now professional basketball.
These kids are literally
making millions of dollars.
Yeah. NIL changed everything.
I grew up going to St.
John's games with my dad.
Well. we're getting
closer at least.
Looks like the last
place Walsh was seen
was at Clancy's.
the bar a few blocks
down the street from the
vacant lot where he was shot.
We're actually closer
than you think we are.
Just found video of Walsh
from the hardware store
across the street from Clancy's.
And there he is. leaving
the bar at 4:34 p.m..
and he's with another guy.
Music to my ears.
Clean angle too.
How about that?
Run it through facial rec.
[suspenseful music]
No need.
It's my brother.
♪
I don't get it.
What's everybody
so worked up about?
Well. you see. Matty. we're
kind of investigating a murder.
You might have been
the last person seen
with the dead guy prior
to him being dead.
So you and Walsh left
the bar together.
Why is that?
Guys. I hope you know
I had nothing to do
with Walsh's death.
You know that. right?
Will you just
answer the question
for once in your life. please?
I was having a beer at Clancy's.
I saw the guy
heading for the door.
I figured I'd walk
over and say hi.
You know. we played against
each other in high school.
I had 17 points.
Fantastic.
Yeah. he remembered
me. No lie.
Said I had one of the prettiest
left-handed jump
shots he'd ever seen.
That's great. Matt. but we're
a little more interested
in the murder than your
jump shot right now. okay?
What'd you guys do
when you left the bar?
Walked for a few blocks
down by the bridge.
I asked if he was gonna
take that Kentucky job.
He didn't really answer me.
Said he was thinking about
it. but that he loved Hudson.
- Okay. then what?
- And then nothing.
He got a phone call.
and he walked away.
That was it.
Was anybody watching
him or waiting for him?
No. not really.
I mean. other than Jackie.
You gonna tell us who Jackie is?
Jackie Costa. He
owns Clancy's.
And what was Jackie Costa doing?
Standing on a box
smoking a cigarette.
Okay. so you and
Walsh part ways.
and Costa is just standing
there smoking a cigarette.
That's it?
Does anybody have a lighter?
Like I said before. I was
here all afternoon working.
Step outside for a few?
Maybe take a walk?
- No.
Maybe take a little smoke break?
I gave it up.
I heard a rumor it was
bad for your health.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah. I heard that one too.
Why are you guys asking
all these questions?
I already told you what
I saw. what I know.
Yeah. yeah.
Well. we talked to someone
who said that they saw Walsh
walking down Sixth
Street. and they thought
that they maybe saw you too.
So. you know. we're
just following up.
He's wrong.
I was inside the
bar all afternoon.
Got it.
- Thanks for your time.
- Mm-hmm.
He's lying his ass off.
about the smoking anyway.
Had a pack of cigarettes
in his jacket pocket.
So Costa's alibi checks out.
Talked to the dishwasher.
the bartender.
two guys who claimed to be
at the bar from 3:00 to 6:00.
and everybody says that Costa
was at the bar the entire time.
and they said he quit smoking.
and they were
adamant about that.
Yeah. those guys would
say he played shortstop
for the Yankees if
he asked them to.
- Mm-hmm.
- Costa is no joke.
I pulled his sheet.
He's got priors for
racketeering. gambling.
assault. and narcotics.
- Oh. busy boy. huh?
- Yeah.
And as suspected. he's a liar.
I found video of him two
blocks from the crime scene
three minutes after
the 911 call at 4:43.
So Costa was not
inside the bar all day.
no matter what his friends say.
- I like him for it.
Yeah. we just gotta
find a way to put him
and Walsh together
prior to the murder.
- Mm-hmm.
- Can you pull more video?
It's pretty thin down
there. Not a lot of cameras.
All right. well.
just... I don't know...
keep pressing the friends.
I mean. you never know.
We can try. but that code
of silence thing is real.
These guys are not gonna budge.
It's how they define
themselves. you know?
Maybe we come at this
from a different angle.
Maybe we try to get
Costa to talk instead.
[tense music]
So what's going on?
This morning. I'm
making an omelet.
You know. avocado.
sausage. peppers. all that.
Doorbell rings. and I'm
thinking it's Amazon.
or maybe it's the lady next
door with the dementia.
or it's...
- For God's sake. Matty.
Yeah. sorry. I get
a little rattled.
I go to the door. and
it's two cops. detectives.
They start asking about Walsh.
What's that got to do with me?
They think you're involved.
Excuse me?
They. uh. kept asking
questions about you.
So that's why you're here?
To find out if what?
If I was involved?
- He's getting suspicious.
- No. he's okay.
Matty can handle this.
Jackie. please.
I'm just trying to help you out.
I mean. I figured it
was best if I came
and just told you what
happened. you know?
- What kind of questions?
- You know. if I...
if I saw you leave
the bar together.
if I saw you and Walsh talking.
if you guys had any bad blood.
I appreciate you
giving me the heads up.
Yeah. yeah. like I said.
I'm just here to help.
Hey. look. I know
you're a good guy.
but I gotta be honest.
You're making me nervous.
He's good. He's still good.
So. what. you wanna
search me for a wire?
It would make me feel better.
♪
I'm insulted. but.
hey. I get it.
These are stressful
times. right?
Go ahead.
♪
Okay. Sorry about that.
You good? [chuckles]
I appreciate you looking out.
The truth is. I might
need some help with this
down the road if these
guys keep sniffing.
Of course. I'm happy to help.
Good.
So these cops happen to tell you
if they had any evidence. video.
witnesses. anything like that?
No. they. uh. they didn't say.
The funny thing is.
I didn't know Walsh.
This former player of
his. this kid Crawford.
he owed me 75 grand.
Now we're cooking.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. What happened?
What happened? What
happened to the feed?
- Hey. no. no.
- What did you do?
- I don't know what happened.
- I got this.
Where's the camera?
- I don't know.
- Where's the button?
Maybe it fell off.
Do not lie to us. Matt.
Do you understand?
Do not lie. Just tell
us what happened.
What happened was...
What happened was I
realized I'm not a snitch.
All right. look.
I'm not ratting out
a friend of mine. a friend
who's been good to me.
who's lent me money.
who's helped me find jobs.
unlike some people. by the way.
- Oh. here we go.
I'm just telling the
truth here. Vince.
You can't even help
yourself. can you?
You know what? I did
what I had to do.
You know. I put my
name on the line.
- Oh. yeah?
- Get out of my face.
Hey. hey. hey. hey.
Watch yourself.
Because I'm not your
brother. You feel me?
You look me in
the eye right now.
You tell me. did Costa
admit to the murder?
Yes or no?
You know what?
We're done talking.
♪
What does that mean.
his wire malfunctioned?
I mean. Matty got nervous. so...
Why?
Because he thought
Costa made him?
I guess so.
Look. we still got
some good information.
Costa said that one of
Walsh's former players
owed him a bunch of money.
So we know that
there's a connection.
So maybe Walsh was there
to smooth things over.
you know. ask for leniency
for the kid or something.
Okay. that's good.
I'm still trying to understand
what happened with
your brother's wire.
- Like I said...
- I know what you said.
But now I wanna
know what happened.
[tense music]
The button fell off.
and Matt stepped on it.
To protect himself?
That's what he said.
And do you believe him?
No.
Okay. well. next time.
lead with the truth.
and then we'll get along better.
Got some good news.
Tracked down the former
player. Crawford.
Got a work address. Let's go.
Yeah. that's... that's true.
I owe Costa 75 grand.
More than that. actually.
because the interest
he's charging.
Why do you owe him the money?
I like to gamble.
You know why Walsh was
going to meet him that day?
Did it have something
to do with your debt?
All right. I needed money.
so I reached out to Coach.
and God bless him.
He said he'd take care of
it. under one condition.
that I get help
for my addiction.
Why?
Y'all don't think
Costa was involved?
We don't know yet. We're
still investigating.
So tell me. did
Coach actually say
that he was gonna
meet with Costa?
I told him where Costa worked.
and Coach said he'd
take care of it.
Now. that's all I know.
- He say when?
No. he just said
that he'd handle it.
Uh-huh.
Look. this is on me. man.
I should have never
gotten him involved.
You know. I was
just a role player.
scoring 3 points
a game. but he...
Look. thanks for being
straight with us. all right?
The dots are all
starting to connect.
and they all lead back to Costa.
Yeah. we're still not there
yet because of your brother.
Had he not killed the
wire. we'd be done by now.
Costa would be in Rikers
staring down murder two.
Tell me I'm wrong.
- Yeah. man. I get it.
But that's just
Matty. all right?
It's just the way he is.
- What?
Do you even hear
yourself right now?
That's not an excuse.
What. you have some biological
urge to cover for his dumb ass?
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Take it easy.
He's still my brother.
And what does that mean. Vince?
You gotta protect him
until the day he dies?
What do you want me to do?
I'm supposed to sell him out?
Let's just...
okay. you're right
about one thing.
Crawford's statement is helpful.
It links Costa and
Walsh. sort of.
It's good enough for a warrant.
[tense music]
♪
NYPD! Do not move!
- Warrant.
- What the hell?
Keep him there.
♪
Crowbar.
[tapping]
Uh-huh.
Looky here. Rolex
with a blue face.
Turn around and put your
hands behind your back.
What are you talking about?
We found a unique and
expensive timepiece
in your desk.
- What the hell does that mean?
It means you're under arrest.
We have the former
player's testimony.
the watch. and
surveillance footage
of Costa two blocks
from the crime scene
a few minutes
after the 911 call.
- What about the murder weapon?
- Police never recovered it.
- Motive?
- I'm not sure.
At the moment. we're
assuming it's something to do
with the former player's debt.
Sounds like Walsh was meeting up
with Costa to pay it off.
Why kill someone who's
giving you money?
It doesn't make sense.
- I know.
We'll keep digging.
[phone buzzing]
Jalen.
Look. I found the
gun in the trash.
I didn't shoot nobody. I swear.
I saw some dude toss it.
You saw someone throw the
gun into the dumpster?
Yeah. a white dude.
Can you describe him.
age. height. body type?
Nah.
So you've just
been walking around
with that gun for three days?
Yeah. but I never shot it.
I just thought it'd
be cool. you know?
No. I don't know.
Because it's not cool to
walk around with a gun.
You hear what I said?
Yeah. I heard you.
You remember where you found
the gun. exact location?
This is Costa.
approximately 100
yards from the dumpster
where the young
man found the gun.
- How close to the crime scene?
- Three blocks.
And the timestamp on the
video is helpful as well.
five minutes after the 911 call.
And we're sure that's
the murder weapon?
Ballistics report just came in.
Okay. good.
So we can tie Costa
to the murder weapon.
Sort of.
It's not ideal.
but it is helpful.
But still no motive.
No. but the evidence is strong.
It should be enough to
compensate for that.
Okay. let's move forward.
Charge him with murder two.
We can tie the
defendant. Jack Costa.
to both the murder weapon
and the crime scene.
We can also tie him to
the victim. Nick Walsh.
and prove he had access to
him on the day of the murder.
No. we don't have an
eyewitness who saw him
shoot Nick Walsh or
video showing him
fleeing the crime. gun in hand.
but the evidence we do have
paints a compelling picture
of what happened that day.
and it will prove beyond
a reasonable doubt
that the defendant
murdered Nick Walsh.
Let me translate what
Mr. Price just said.
We have a lousy case.
and we aren't really sure that
Jack Costa committed the crime.
Nick Walsh was an
animated and fiery coach
with lots of notoriety
and lots of enemies.
He was a hometown hero
who helped lead Hudson
to unprecedented success.
but he was on the
verge of leaving.
chasing bigger. better.
shinier dreams at a new school.
He was in the middle of
negotiating a contract
that would be worth
over $100 million.
The fans were upset.
They thought he was disloyal.
They accused him of using
Hudson as a stepping stone.
Like it or not.
there were thousands
of irrational and
disgruntled fans
who thought Nick
Walsh was a traitor.
and any one of them could
have pulled that trigger.
including the teenage boy
who just so happens to
find the murder weapon
and who just so happens
to be a die-hard
Hudson U Basketball fan.
Bottom line. there's
no motive here.
Jack Costa is a
hardworking businessman
who never met Nick Walsh.
so he had absolutely
no reason to kill him.
Did your husband own a watch?
- Yes.
- Can you describe it?
It was a Rolex. blue
face. white markers.
and a platinum-and-gold band.
Does this watch look like
the one your husband owned?
Yes. definitely.
That's it.
Let the record reflect
the watch Mrs. Walsh
just identified was
the watch recovered
from the defendant's office.
- So noted.
- Nothing further.
Your husband's watch
wasn't registered. correct?
So there's no way of proving
that that's the same watch.
I'm not sure.
One of Nick's former players
gave it to him the day
after he signed a new contract.
That may be true.
but you don't know
that that's the same watch.
No. that's the watch.
Nick wore it every day.
He said it reminded him
what his job really was.
to help kids achieve
their dreams.
The crime lab tested the watch
that the police found
in my client's bar
for your husband's DNA.
The test came back negative.
I didn't know.
One more thing you
probably didn't know.
the watch you just looked
at. the Submariner.
it's a very popular watch.
There's literally thousands
of them in existence.
the same brand.
model. face. color.
The manufacturer released
1.200 of them just this year.
So there's no way of determining
that the watch
you just looked at
actually belonged
to your husband.
[tense music]
I... I suppose you're right.
I know. Sam. we're looking.
but I'm telling you.
there's nothing else to move on.
I get it.
Problem is. the defense
is picking us apart.
so we need something
else. something new.
preferably something
that explains
why Costa actually killed Walsh.
Look. we have zero evidence
that points to motive.
And trust me. Costa's friends.
they're not cooperating.
These guys eat. drink. and
sleep this omertà nonsense.
Someone in that crowd has
to have a shred of humanity
and realize that when a
person kills an innocent man.
he has to pay.
I'm not so sure about that.
Sorry. Vin.
All the beer in my fridge
actually has alcohol in it.
Maybe it shouldn't.
Come on. don't start with all
that "bad genes" crap again.
Listen. Matt. you need
to tell me what you know.
all right? What
you really know.
And you need to
tell me right now.
Mm-hmm. yeah. I already did.
Did he confess?
Did he say that he shot Walsh?
I don't wanna get
involved. all right?
It's not my job.
- God. what... [stammers]
What is wrong with you. huh?
Walsh had a wife. He
had two little girls.
And you don't care
that your friend
put two bullets in his chest?
Of course. I care.
Matt. if you know something.
this is the only way
to get rid of the gun charge.
- Oh. please.
There's gotta be 100 ways to
make the gun charge go away.
There's not. There's one.
And this is it.
I can't do it. I'm
not that kind of guy.
You're not that kind of guy?
The kind of guy that
thinks that murderers
should actually go to prison?
You're my brother.
but we're different.
I look out for my
friends. no matter what.
Are you listening to
yourself right now. huh?
You actually believe this crap?
Let me tell you something.
This is not some Scorsese movie
where you and your friends
kick it around the neighborhood
spouting off all this tough
guy talk with no consequences.
This is real.
And you need to look out
for yourself right now.
You understand me?
Not some punk named Costa
who doesn't care about you.
This is the moment. Matt.
This is your moment.
and this is your last chance.
♪
Costa said that Walsh
was a good guy. you know.
and that he cared
about his players.
and so he thought he
had him over a barrel.
Meaning what?
Thought he could jam him up.
You know. ask for more
money than the kid owed.
Uh-huh. Can you
be more specific?
Kid owed. like.
75 grand. I think.
Costa was gonna ask for...
I don't know... 150.
[chuckles]
What else did he tell you?
That when he asked Walsh.
he got upset. you know?
Real upset.
[pensive music]
Things got out of hand.
Did Costa confess
to shooting him?
Like I said. Walsh got angry.
threatened to kick his ass.
Costa did what he had to do.
Those your words or his?
His.
Yeah.
When we're in court.
answer the questions
like you did just now.
You're doing the
right thing. Matt.
♪
Did you and the defendant
ever discuss the circumstances
of Nick Walsh's murder?
Yeah.
Did he tell you
why he was meeting
Mr. Walsh that afternoon?
Yeah. he said. uh...
said Walsh was gonna
pay off the debt
of one of his former players.
He say anything else?
No. not really.
Did he mention any
other reason for meeting
Mr. Walsh that day?
Was he planning to
discuss or demand
anything else from Mr. Walsh?
[tense music]
Mr. Riley. did the
defendant tell you
what he planned
to ask Mr. Walsh
when they met up in person?
No.
Never... never told you what
they planned to discuss?
No.
Did the defendant ever tell
you who shot Mr. Walsh?
No.
I'd like to request
a brief recess.
What's going on?
You said you were
willing to testify.
I guess I changed my mind.
Are you serious?
Guess so.
♪
What the hell is
the matter with you?
This is a murder trial. Matt.
You understand that?
You're under oath.
Yeah. I know.
I thought I could do
it. Vin. but. uh...
[chuckles] I can't do it.
You know that this
is your last...
Your Honor. the
witness's answers
are inconsistent with
his previous statements.
As such. I'd like to treat
him as a hostile witness.
Yes. I'll allow it.
Mr. Riley. you presented
a sworn affidavit
to me stating that the defendant
planned to exploit
Mr. Walsh's compassion
for his former player.
Objection. Hearsay.
Your Honor. it was
a sworn statement.
I'm offering it for
impeachment purposes only.
Okay. but that's
as far as it goes.
Overruled.
The defendant's plan
was to ask Mr. Walsh
for double the amount
Jordan Crawford
actually owed. correct?
I don't know
anything about that.
And because of this.
the two men fought.
Objection.
This is being offered as
the truth. not impeachment.
Sustained.
Mr. Price. for
impeachment purposes only.
I won't ask again.
Your refusal to
cooperate here today.
to not answer my questions
in a truthful manner
is based on your desire
to help the defendant?
I'm just telling
you what I know.
You think it's a cowardly act
to testify against a friend.
regardless of his
guilt or innocence.
Isn't that true?
That snitching is a
crime unto itself.
that ratting someone out is
an unforgivable betrayal.
I don't know what your point is.
My point is that you
agreed to tell the truth.
but you didn't do it.
You couldn't do it.
because in your mind.
it's better to let
a killer go free
than testify against a friend.
Am I right? Is
that how you think?
Better to be a stand-up guy
and keep your mouth shut.
Yeah. You're damn right it is.
Even if the consequence
of that silence
is to let a killer walk free?
That doesn't bother you?
Not in the least.
♪
Nothing further.
Ms. Gallo?
No questions.
♪
Please rise.
In the matter of
People versus Costa.
has the jury reached a verdict?
Yes. we have. Your Honor.
How do you find?
We find the defendant guilty.
Members of the jury. I'd like
to thank you for your service.
Court is adjourned.
[gavel bangs]
♪
Guess it all worked out. huh?
Yeah.
Just happy for the
Walsh family. man.
They really needed the W.
Yeah. so did you.
You know. Vince.
you're a great cop.
People really respect you.
But if Costa had
been acquitted...
♪
[knocking]
Matty. it's Vince.
[pop music playing]
♪
Yeah. I'll be right back.
[chuckles] What are you doing?
You know. I wish you'd called.
I. uh. I got a lady
friend over. you know?
You and your ladies.
Yeah. well. at least I'm
good at something. right?
Listen. we gotta take a ride.
All right. Where?
The precinct.
What are you talking about?
The gun case.
They're gonna charge you.
Get out of here. What
are you talking...
you said you were
gonna make a call.
make it go away.
Yeah. well. I guess
I changed my mind.
[tense music]
Look. Vin. I'm sorry. all right?
But you gotta help me out.
You gotta give me
another chance here.
I'll come through.
- I can't do it anymore. Matt.
- I promise.
- I can't do it.
Come on. let's go.
Come on.
♪
[dramatic music]
[wolf howls]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm